radian6.com 2012-06-28

# Privacy Policy « Radian6 - Social media monitoring tools, social media engagement software and social CRM and marketing from the industry leader in social analytics.

**Last Updated: September 1, 2010**

**Radian6’s Privacy Commitment  
**Radian6, a division of salesforce.com Canada _Corporation_ ( **“Radian6”** ) is committed to protecting the privacy, confidentiality and security of your personal information. This privacy policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) is intended to inform you about our practices relating to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information through your use of the Radian6 website ( **“Site”** ) and by your use of Radian6’s services ( **“Services”** ).

This privacy policy applies only to personal information related to users of the Site and the Services.

This policy is consistent with the principles of the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_ ( **“PIPEDA”** ), which sets out rules and guidelines for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. By using this Site and/or the Services, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy and are consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Changes to Privacy Policy  
**Radian6 reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, so please check back periodically and make note of the effective date at the top of the policy. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will post a notice on our homepage and update the policy posted on our website. Your continued use of this Site or any Services after we post an updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the new terms and their application to your use of the Site or any Services

**Accountability  
**Radian6 is accountable for all personal information that it collects and is under its control. For the purposes of this privacy policy, “personal information” is information about an identifiable customer, their authorized representatives or a visitor to the Site, but excludes business contact information (such as business name, title, address and phone number). This Site is controlled, operated and administered entirely with Canada. If you are located outside Canada, please note that the personal information you provide to us will be transferred and stored in Canada. By accessing or using our Site, you hereby consent to such transfer.

**What Information Do We Collect?  
**Radian6 collects only personal information that is necessary to provide customers and their authorized representatives with our Services, such as name, address, billing information, login name, and email address. We only collect information directly from the individual concerned, except that an organization establishing a corporate account may provide Radian6 with the minimum information necessary to set up the related user accounts.

We do not routinely disclose personal information to any third parties except with your consent. (In certain circumstances described below, we may disclose your personal information to third parties.) Any secondary use of personal information for marketing purposes is only done with your consent and you are able to opt-out from such use.

**Limits for Collecting, Using, Disclosing and Keeping Personal Information  
**Radian6 will not use personal information for any other purpose than identified at or before the time of collection. At the time that any personal information is collected, Radian6 will inform you of the purposes for which the information is being collected and will obtain express consent, unless such purposes are reasonably obvious to the individual and where consent can be implied.

In most cases, personal information is used only to provide you with requested Services, such as access to the Site and to administer the Services in manner described in the applicable contract between Radian6 and you or your organization. We may also use personal information to maintain, protect, and improve our Services and develop new Services and protect the rights or property of Radian6 or its users. You can withdraw your consent at any time, but if you do so Radian6 will not be able to provide you with Services. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, you are not permitted to access the Site.

Such information is generally used to provide you with the Services requested, as well as our demos, webinars, training programs, and newsletters subscriptions. Personal Information may also be used to make recommendations to you about other Services offered by Radian6 based upon our assessment of your social media monitoring needs, unless you indicate that you do not wish to receive such offers or recommendations. If we propose to change or add additional purposes to the use of personal information, we will make reasonable efforts to obtain the individual’s consent for such changed or additional uses. Reasonable efforts to notify individuals include posting an updated privacy policy that describes the change.

Radian6 does not sell, trade or otherwise transfer your personal information to third parties under any circumstances. Radian6 may, from time to time, use service providers to perform services on its behalf but all service providers are required to comply with this policy, safeguard the personal information and to only use the personal information to provide the contracted services. Our service providers are restricted from using or disclosing personal information transferred to them for any purpose other than the provision of services to Radian6.

There are circumstances where Radian6 may disclose personal information without notice or consent, for example to its lawyers or to collect debts owing to Radian6, for purposes relating to law enforcement investigations or where otherwise required by law to disclose the personal information. We may also collect, use and disclose personal information to enforce our Site policies or to protect Radian6’s rights and intellectual property or the rights of others using our Site or Services. Otherwise, Radian6 will not use or disclose personal information without the knowledge or consent of the individual except as authorized by applicable law.

Personal information may be disclosed to a purchaser or a potential purchaser or all or a part of the Radian6 business. In the event of a sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of Radian6 (or a portion of it), we will require any such buyer to agree to treat your personal information in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of the transfer.

Radian6 retains personal information only as long as is necessary to provide the individual with the requested Service or requested information. In some cases, however, legal reporting or retention requirements necessitate that Radian6 retain information for a specific amount of time.

**Accuracy of and Access to Personal Information Collected  
**You have the right to access your personal information held by Radian6 (subject to limited lawful exceptions), and as the case may be, to request that the information be corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete. You may also inform us if you do not wish to receive offers and promotions regarding our Services.

On written request of, you may view or edit your personal information as collected by Radian6. Radian6 will inform you of what personal information it has about you, what it is being used for and, a general account of its use. To make a request, please send a letter, email or fax addressed to our Privacy Officer at the address indicated below. In any written request, please include the following information: name, contact details, and the nature of the request, for example: view and/or edit information, inquire regarding use and/or disclosure. We may require that you provide additional information to assist in finding your personal information or to verify your identity.

**IP Addresses and Anonymous Browsing  
**You are able to use some Services anonymously without registering and providing personal information about yourself. As with most website operators, we maintain server logs that provide us with general information about Site visitors. This information may include a your general location, the domain name you used to access Radian6, the type and version of browser you are using, and your Internet Service provider. This information is used by Radian6 to assist us in administering our Site.

Apart from the collection of this anonymous information, you will always know when Radian6 is collecting personal and other information from you and, consequently, you may decline to provide such information at any time.

**Use of Cookies  
**Our website uses “cookies”. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by our website server software to assist us in understanding how you use the website. Cookies are sometimes used to help us save your preferences to avoid having to re-enter data, so that when you visit the Site again at another time, your settings are saved. Using cookies, we can understand how a visitor uses our website, but the user will always be anonymous if the user is not logged-in. Cookies are not required for the proper use of this Site.

We may also use “per-session cookies”, which are used to store technical information only within a session particular visit. These cookies are on your computer only while you are visiting our website and are deleted from the cache when the user closes the session. Per-session cookies are frequently used by websites using content management systems to store session information as the user navigates to multiple pages in a site.

**Links to Other Websites  
**This Privacy Policy only applies to Radian6’s collection, use and disclosure of information, and does not apply to any information that may be collected by or submitted to any other websites. Please refer to the applicable privacy policies of other sites to understand how they collect, use or disclose personal information.

**Safeguards  
**Radian6 implements industry-standard safeguards to protect personal information. Given the nature of the internet, any internet communications between you and Radian6 can be intercepted. While Radian6 strives to protect personal information, it cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to it or received from it electronically.

Your personal information will only be stored and processed on servers or computers located within Canada.

Internally, access to personal information is restricted to employees who need access to the information in order to perform their duties, that is, to provide you with the Services you have requested.

**Challenging Compliance  
**If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or about Radian6’s handling of personal information, you may address those concerns to Radian6’s Privacy Officer:

**Privacy Officer  
**E-mail address: [privacy@radian6.com  
](mailto:privacy@radian6.com)Phone: 506.452.9039  
Fax: 506.452.2938  
Mail: Radian6, a division of salesforce.com Canada Corporation  
30 Knowledge Park Drive  
Fredericton, New Brunswick  
E3C 2R2
